

CONTACT

+381 60 4480 446



✓ radivojevicveljko@gmail.com



Belgrade, Serbia



GitHub:

https://github.com/veljkoRad



Portfolio :

https://veljkorad.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Belgrade | 2011 - 2018

• Computer-aided design/manufacturing -Cad/Cam systemsnt

"POLITEHNIKA" - SCHOOL FOR NEW **TECHNOLOGIES**

Belgrade | 2007 - 2011

• Computer control technician- Cnc Machines

SKILLS

HTML & CSS:

• Flexbox, Grid, Semantic Html, **Bootstrap Library**

JAVA SCRIPT:

• Data types, Array Methods, Functions, Loops and Iterations, Asynchronous, API, JSON, DOMManipulation, ES6, Axios

JAVA SCRIPT LIBRARY:

• React.Js, Material UI, Competence

WORPDRESS:

• Custom WordPress theme development

VELJKO RADIVOJEVIC

WFB DFVFI OPFR

PROFILE

Passionate frontend developer with one year of experience in PPC

Proven track record in creating 100+ successful landing pages.

Enthusiastic about coding, continuous learning, and problem-solving with a proactive mindset.

Self-taught and always eager to expand my knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, PPC Marketing

2023 - PRESENT

Online International Marketing d.o.o

- Landing page development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript),
- WordPress site creation,
- HTML email template design
- Basic PHP/SQL integration.

Cnc Programmer/Operator

2019 - 2022

Private project

• Selection of creative wooden toys for children that meet environmental requirements, are safe for children and also affordable for everyone.

Cnc Programmer/Operator

2020 - 2021

Beopumpe

• Selection of creative wooden toys for children that meet environmental requirements, are safe for children and also affordable for everyone.

Cnc operator

2018 - 2020

Konelek Aerospace Engineering

· Worked as operator on different types of Macho Cnc and Haas milling machines.

PROGRAMMING RELEVANT COURSES

· Programming - Faculty of Mechanical Engineering, Belgrade

On this course I learned basics of "C" programming language.

· Web Deisgn in mechanical engineering - Faculty of Mechanical Engineering, Belgrade

Html, CSS, SQL basics

 Computer Tools - Faculty of Mechanical Engineering, Belgrade Working with MatLab, drawing 2d & 3D graphics, solving equations.